decorpad.com 2018-09-30

# Privacy Policy

DecorPad.com maintains the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information we obtain from our members. To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools to assist in the protection of your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, so we make no guarantees. We do not disclose personal information to any outside party. We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to any third party, unless legally required to do so. Any information we collect from our members will be used in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic, understand member needs and trends, and to improve our services. This information is for internal use only and will not be distributed or sold to any parties outside DecorPad.

The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personal information) in connection with your use of these public forums. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Site.

We are not responsible for the content of any websites which may be linked to DecorPad.com. These links are provided for your convenience only and you access them at your own risk. The privacy policies and the practices of websites outside DecorPad and all of its services are beyond our control. It is your responsibility to read and understand the privacy policies of any and all websites you visit on the web.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: http://google.com/privacy_ads.html

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on decorpad.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to decorpad.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL <http://google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: [Google AdSense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and [VigLink](http://www.viglink.com/static/policies/ftc).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on DecorPad.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

DecorPad.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. decorpad.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
